You have to understand, most of these people
are not ready to be unplugged.
And many of them are so inured, so hopelessly
dependent on the system...
I know you're out there. I can feel you now.
I know that you're afraid.
You're afraid of us.
We've been trying to reach you, Detective.
Please, sit down.
I'm afraid I have some difficult news
about your partner.
The diner was empty except for the two of them.
Nobody saw a thing.
That's not possible. Someone always sees something.
She left three months ago and never came back.
Her daughter still waits by the window every evening.
Some people don't want to be found.
The letter arrived the morning after the funeral.
It was dated six weeks earlier.
He knew. He knew the whole time
and said nothing.
I've been doing this job for twenty-two years
and I have never seen anything like it.
Then maybe it's time you started
looking a little harder.
Whatever happens next, I need you to know
I made this choice on my own.